Come on, come on, come on.
Wow, it's opening up!
The tomato sauce is soaking up the flavor.
What a surprise!
Enjoy!
Wow!
This is Okuma Day from Sakurazaka 46.
I'm Okuma Day from Sakurazaka46, and today, I'm going to show you something on my YouTube channel.
I've always wanted to go to a homeless shelter.
I've been wanting to go to a homeless place for a long time.
I'm on my way there now!
I've been living in the countryside for a long time.
I've lived in the countryside, so I've never been to a homeless place.
I've never been to a place like this in Tokyo.
I didn't have a homeless place like this in Tokyo.
The last place I went was
Takayama or something.
but I haven't been there since I got tired.
I haven't been there since I got tired.
I'm not sure if this is private or not.
I guess it's not private.
But it's been 5 years since I've been to a private place.
I haven't been there in 5 years.
It's a place I've always wanted to visit.
That's it, isn't it?
Wow, they're getting closer!
I'm so nervous!
I'm nervous.
Wow, Mr. Jonas!
Wow, they open at 8:00 a.m.
Wait, how do you get into a family restaurant?
How do you get into a family restaurant? Hello?
I'm scared.
Wow, scary.
Oh, no.
Ta-da!
Jonathan.
How do you get in?
Just go in like a normal person, right?
Heh heh heh.
I'm nervous.
Say hello.
I don't say hello. I don't say hello.
Hang in there, hang in there, hang in there.
Wow, it's open.
Oh, wow.
Oh, wow! Oh, wow!
There's another one.
There's a rumble machine? Wow!
Wow, this is so cute!
I ate Ceri's food.
Good luck, good luck!
Good job!
Ta-da!
So many people!
Oh, no, no, no...
Please, I'm alone.
Yes, please.
Do you want a squish?
Thank you very much.
Sterilize, sterilize, sterilize.
Oh, my God.
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh.
You have a lot of them.
For school attendees inadequate anie
wh
outline
very erroneously correct.
This one.
means?
In order, in order, in order, in order.
You mean you're going to do it this way?
This is so hard, so hard, so hard.
I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know
I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know
I don't know... I'm scared... I'm scared...
Ha-ha-ha-ha...
This is, uh, this is a typical Camino menu, right? Oh, it's so big!
Look at the menu!
Wow, it's huge!
Wow!
Wow, there are so many kinds of food!
What should I do? I want something family-like... family-like...
Hamburger steak!
I can't decide!
I don't know what to do.
Hurry, hurry, hurry!
Hurry up, hurry up!
I think I'll have tomato spaghetti with eggplant and bacon!
Oh, this might be a tough one!
What's this?
Remove it!
It's off.
I'll start ordering.
Here, here, here.
One, 161.
Moving on.
How about this one?
Wow!
They recommend salads too? This one.Salads are also recommended? This one.
Lunch Salad Set? Lunch set salad?
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
What's this?
Which one? Which one?
It's okay if you don't want it.
It's kind of hard, so don't do it.
Oh, wait, you made it better.
Okay. - Yeah.
Yeah.
Drink bar.
Over 30 kinds?
Wow, do you guys do a wink bar?
It's a little challenging for a beginner.
All right, all right, all right, all right, all right, all right.
Fix your order.
Yes!
Yay!
Heh heh heh heh.
It's beeping.
Order submitted.
Thank you very much.
Please take from the drink corner
Water.
Where's the drinks corner?
I'm going alone.
Do you want to give up your water?
I think I'll pass on the water.
No, but I'd like a glass of water.
Okay.
Let's go.
Uh, where's the drink corner?
Huh?
If there's, if there's... oh, there it is!
Excuse me... Oh, here it is... water...
What's this? What's this? Where do you get the cups? This is it, isn't it?
This is it, right? Thank you very much.
Do you want ice? No, I don't want ice.
You want me to push the glass like this? Oh, water, yes...
I've finally made it across! Thank you very much.
Thank you very much. And here's your water.
You push it like this, right?
Wow, I missed the other drink bar!
Oh no, the drink bar is too difficult!
I'll take a look at the other drink bar. There are some juices at the back of the bar.
I see.
Oh, you actually put ice and choose your juice.
I see... I see...
It's hard, it's hard, it's hard to do!
Oh, I got water!
There you go!
Can I see what kind of people are here?
What kind of people?
Hey, come on!
Go around.
Oh!
One person so much.
Whoa! There's one person!
Oh, my gosh!
Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey.
Run, run, run!
There's one guy. Oh, my God.
Control, display, surface, display, control.
When is the pussycat robot coming?
There's the management robot.
Oh, you mean you took it.
That's great.
Well, I'm surprised.
Surprise!
Amazing!
Oh, my God!
Is this the cat's mat?
Wow, that's amazing!
Please take a picture!
Oh, you mean I can take a picture of it because it's glowing?
Oh, kitty... uh, let's take a couple of shots.
Oh, my gosh! My first time! Amazing!
Oh, it smells so good. You're going to take a picture of this.
Oh, it's so warm. Wow, wow, wow, wow, wow, wow.
There we go. There we go.
I got it. Oh, and?
Oh, clever! I was just about to hit "done".
Oh, great!
Boom, boom, boom.
Wow, smart!
Oh, I'm so happy. It's a kitty robot.
Oh, my gosh, that's a first.
Oh, here it is. Here it is.
It's here. - Ta-da!
Rustic bacon pasta.
Bon appétit!
Oh!
You've got to have chocolate.
Wow, what am I going to do?
I'll have the Nutzle Cartabesse.
Delicious!
It soaks up the flavor of the tomato sauce.
Oh, yes, chocolate ponzu!
That's it!
Cheese!
Delicious!Delicious!
Very milky.
Yes, yes.
I was really just thinking on my own.
Do you know what a flower subscription service is?
I'd like to try it.
I'd like to try to put a few flowers on a piece of paper.
I was wondering if I could find a vase for it.
Just when I was thinking about it
Yui Kobayashi gave me a vase as a gift.
Ms. Yui Kobayashi gave me a vase as a gift.
I had no choice but to start
I knew I had no choice but to start
I thought
I thought so?
I thought you haven't started yet...
But there have been many of them recently.
I wish something like this would happen.
Wait, maybe it's happening now, too.
Maybe even now.
I often see YouTubers
I often see YouTubers eating alone.
I thought, "I want to do that," and I did it!
I'm so happy!
I'm going to eat.
A woman just came in.
A woman just came in by herself.
She's working.
What? It's a charging hole.
Is it there?
A charging port.
You can charge it, too.
Oh.
Oh, you mean just for those special seats?
Oh, how do we get out? Oh, my God!
We can do it right here.
Does everybody know about this? I don't have to show you.
Ta-da!
Uh, 50 yen, please.
Oh, wow.
I thought it was just for that seat.
I thought it was just for that seat, but it's for all of them.
Wow.
Oh, so you're saying I can stay longer?
What a nice family restaurant.
That's great.
I'll finish with cheese.
Yeah. - Mm-hmm.
Mm-hmm.
Mm-hmm. Mm-hmm.
It was delicious!
Thank you for the food.
And now...
Let's see what's for dessert.
What a surprise.
The cat's coming through!
Oh, wow!
Oh, she's going to ride on the bottom step too!
Oh, no. Oh, no.
Well, I'd like to call that kitty again.
I think I'll take this one.
Mango
Mango Rare Cheese Bowls
It's the second time, indeed.
How about this one?
You already know he's coming.
When are you waiting for this dish?
Oh, great.
I'll confirm it myself.
Oh, here we go. Get the water out of the drink intersection.
Yes, the water I just got.
What? They do take-out.
Great, oh, here comes the cat.
Hiya!
Wow, I've seen this so many times, it's still fun.
Wow, they even bring these tiny things.
This?
Please take your food.
No, no, no, I'm sorry.
Spoon and...
Touch your head.
There you go.
That's great.
Ha-ha-ha-ha-ha.
Wow.
I'll see you soon.
Here it comes... here it comes...
Here we go.
Boom, boom, boom!
Mango! Mango, mango, mango!
Oh, it's so cute!
Bon appétit!
Yummy!
Delicious!
Oh, my gosh!
What is this?
It tastes so much like mango!It tastes like mango so much!
strange
It's so strange!
What is this?
Delicious!
You can eat this, right?
Is it normal to eat it?
Mint?
I'm sure they would eat it if they had to.
Today is the anniversary of Hamilles.
It's not just for Hamiles.
It's not just about Hamilles, it's also about recommendations.
One person, one place...
Chicken
Or Conveyor belt sushi by yourself...
Ramen by yourself
And so on and so forth.
If this YouTube gives me a push
I think I could do it.
But I think I can grow if I do it alone.
See you!
Thank you for your hard work!
I'm very satisfied with my first time at a family restaurant by myself!
I'm so happy!
This is really an anniversary in my life!
I'm so nervous to answer the door!
I should just go out like a normal person, right?
Just pay the bill and leave.
I'll just pay the bill and go home.
Thank you very much! This is the place to remember.
Thank you for the food.
I'm sorry I came out...
Are you sure you're okay with this?
I just want to enjoy myself and have a good meal...
But I was really nervous before I came in.
I can't believe I came out with such a warm feeling.
I thought that family restaurants are wonderful!
If you want to continue to support my Solitary Gourmet
If you support me, please let me know many places I can go
If you want to support me in the future, please let me know many places that I can go and challenge myself!
Depending on what you tell me, it might become a series!
So, if you like this video, please like and subscribe to my channel.
If you like this video, please like and subscribe to my channel!
Please support Rei Osawa's gourmet trip!